[{"id":"lv9m3ubl","question":"Böbrek yetmezliği hangi organ kaynaklıdır?","answerOptions":["Liver","Heart","Kidney","Stomach"],"answer":"Kidney","type":"multiple choice","hardness":"medium","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"Turkish","lockedAnswer":"English"},{"id":"lv9m3x6p","question":"In which section can piston problems occur on a ship?","answerOptions":["Motor","Armada","Pupa","Döviz"],"answer":"Motor","type":"multiple choice","hardness":"medium","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"English","lockedAnswer":"English"},{"id":"lv9m3xw3","question":"Скільки часу людина може прожити без води?","answerOptions":[],"answer":"3 дні","type":"fill in the blank","hardness":"easy","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"Ukrainian","lockedAnswer":"Ukrainian"},{"id":"lv9m3vo1","question":"How many types of kidney failure are there?","answerOptions":["1","2","3","4"],"answer":"2","type":"multiple choice","hardness":"hard","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"English","lockedAnswer":"English"},{"id":"lv9m3tbx","question":"How to solve piston problems on a ship?","answerOptions":["Repair","Change","Buffer","Living"],"answer":"Change","type":"multiple choice","hardness":"hard","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"English","lockedAnswer":"English"},{"id":"lv9m3wd9","question":"In which condition can kidney failure occur?","answerOptions":[],"answer":"High blood pressure","type":"fill in the blank","hardness":"easy","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"English","lockedAnswer":"English"},{"id":"lv9m3qpa","question":"Болезнь почек неизлечима.","answerOptions":["Correct","Wrong"],"answer":"Wrong","type":"true and false","hardness":"medium","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"Russian","lockedAnswer":"English"},{"id":"lv9m3ug3","question":"На каждом судне возникают проблемы с поршнем.","answerOptions":["Верно","Неверно"],"answer":"Неверно","type":"true and false","hardness":"easy","marksWorth":1,"lockedQuestion":"Russian","lockedAnswer":"Russian"}]